A couple weeks ago Google released
Gemini 3.5 flash, an LLM that's cheap,
insanely fast, and a lot of people are
finding builds beautiful front-ends,
user interfaces that actually look like
they're handcrafted by a human. And
trust me, LLMs are usually pretty bad at
that. And then just a week later,
Anthropic drops Opus 4.8, a reasoning
powerhouse that just generally does
really well on longer running agentic
engineering tasks. And so now we have
these two new models that have their
strengths and weaknesses. And you might
think for your AI coding workflow you
have to pick one. But what I'm really
excited to show you today is a workflow
that I built. GitHub linked in the
description, you can use this today,
that mixes providers. So it's a workflow
using both Opus and Gemini 3.5 flash to
build beautiful full-stack web
applications. And so we're using the new
Gemini to design the user interface, but
then Opus is still doing all the
planning for things like the page copy
and any of the integrations to really
make it a full-stack. And what really
inspired me to build this workflow, and
I'll show you how it works and how to
use it in this video,
is I've been doing a lot of testing
recently with Gemini 3.5 flash both in
the new version of antigravity and in Pi
as my coding agent harness. And it's
been able to build user interfaces that
look like this. This was a one-shot in
the new antigravity. Insanely
impressive. I mean, this looks way
better than what you'd usually make with
Claude code lovable bull. Not new at
least for a one-shot. A lot less obvious
that this is made by a coding agent. I
mean, there's still a couple of things
here that make it obvious like this
header at the top you see way too much
in LLM sites, but overall this is a
really, really good starting point. And
so yeah, Gemini crushes the UI. But one
thing that I noticed as I was building
these sites is the UI looks good, but
the information itself, the page copy,
was often pretty hallucinated. And so
like like looking at the benchmarks
here, Gemini 3.5 Flash seems pretty good
compared to other models like Opus and
Sonnet. But like in the end, Opus 4.8
benchmarks in my own experience and a
lot of people's experiences is just way
better at reasoning overall. And so,
this workflow combines the best of both
worlds. Opus isn't as good as building
front ends, but it sure is better
designing the page copy, making sure it
doesn't hallucinate the actual
information and integrations for the
front end. And then sort of the
secondary benefit here is Gemini 3.5
Flash being a lot cheaper. We can spend
a ton of tokens designing the actual UI
while still paying a lot less. Like the
price here
$1.50 for every 1 million input tokens.
It is a lot more expensive using Opus
4.8. So, mixing providers for the sake
of cost and because we're leaning on the
strengths for different parts of our
workflow.
So, I want to explain the workflow with
you at a high level, each one of the
nodes that we have here and how we're
mixing providers. I know it's a longer
workflow, but we can use this to
one-shot some pretty impressive websites
like this one I built right here, a deep
space catalog. I built just for a
demonstration for this video. But yeah,
the UI looks really good and the page
copy is perfect. It has a full back end
that Opus built as well. This is the
kind of thing we can build with this
workflow in a single shot. And then I
also just want to cover how you can use
this workflow and just generally some
best practices that I built into this
that you can have as a takeaway no
matter the harness you're building,
mixing providers in any way.
And then in the repository for this
workflow that I have linked in the
description, I have a read me here that
you can point your coding agent at to
set up everything. So, it'll copy the
skills over into whatever folder you
want to create your application. And
then it'll help you set up Pi with
OpenRouter to have access to Gemini 3.5
Flash. And later I'll show how you could
use Anti-Gravity as well. So, I just
used open router as my way to work with
Gemini.
And so, we have all of the skills really
for each one of the steps in the
workflow that we have here. And then, if
you want to run everything as a
one-shot, I also have the Archon
workflow. So, I'm not going to focus on
this in this video, but Archon is my
open source harness builder. This is a
workflow that takes all of these skills,
and it combines it together into a
single execution. So, the agent will go
through every single one of these steps
autonomously. So, really, really cool.
But, I want to more focus on the skills
here so that you aren't, you know,
forced to use my tool. And then, also
it's better to just kind of explain
things step-by-step in that way. So,
I'll go through the workflow and then
show you running the skills
simultaneously. So, at a high level, the
most important thing to understand for
this workflow is every step is a
separate coding agent session. And the
way that they communicate with each
other is by passing off a handoff
documents. So, every single step is
going to output a markdown document that
is immediately read at the start of the
next node. And so, for example, with our
first step here, we kind of just survey
the repo and the spec initially with
Sonnet. And so, all that initial
exploration, we summarize it in
context.md, and then that is read in our
plan step. So, there are two big reasons
that we designed the workflow in this
way. The first and more obvious one is
that there's not really a way to mix
providers in a single conversation,
right? Like, I can't really just start
with open assistant Claude code, and
then transition that same context window
into Gemini with either Pi or
anti-gravity. It's just not possible to
do that really. And so, that's why we
designed the workflow first to be each
step is a separate session. It also
makes it very easy for us to experiment.
Like, I can try in just a couple
minutes, I can swap exploration to use
Gemini with Pi as well. Or, I could have
integrate use Pi with Kimmy K 2.6. Like,
I can can this workflow and really
experiment and find the best mix of
providers. And the other equally
important reason is we want to have
every step of this workflow focused on a
single task. Large language models, even
the best ones like Opus right now, get
overwhelmed when you try to have them do
too much at once. Like there's no way
for a larger workflow like this, I'm
going to try to have Opus handle the
whole thing, like exploration and then
planning and then building the UI and
then doing the integrations for full
stack. I can guarantee it will fall flat
on its face for anything more than a
trivial web application. That's why we
want to split things up. As long as we
have a good process for hand-offs here,
we're going to get the best results when
every step, every coding agent session,
is focused on one particular thing. And
so, yes, there is a lot of prompt and
context engineering that went into the
skills for the hand-off process. We
really have to make sure they're
communicating effectively, and that's
why I'm excited to give this as a
resource for you cuz there's a lot of
effort I put into it. But assuming you
have that taken care of and designed
well, this is going to give you the best
results. Now, for a larger workflow like
this, it's not like you can one-shot
every web application. Like I want to be
clear up front, but it's going to be
great for building any kind of proof of
concept or MVP for even non-trivial
full-stack applications. The sponsor of
today's video is Sonar, specifically
their SonarQube advanced security
product. The reality right now is that
30 to 40% of code is already being
written by AI at a lot of companies, and
that number is only going up. But what
most companies aren't solving for fast
enough is verification. If your AI is
going to write code at machine speed,
you also need verification that runs at
machine speed. And that matters nowhere
more than security. Case in point, just
a couple of months ago we had the big
Axios NPM package vulnerability. There
was a version that shipped with a remote
access Trojan. That, my friend, is bad
news. And the The is if you're using
Cloud Code or whatever coding agent, it
might have brought that malicious
version into your codebase without you
even realizing. And so, your machine is
infected before you even know it.
Really, what it comes down to is we need
our coding agents to have a way to
verify the security of dependencies as
they're bringing them into our
codebases. And that is what SonarQube's
advanced security gives us. You can
think of it like a circuit breaker. When
your coding agent wants to bring in an
unverified dependency, it can lean on
SonarQube advanced security and the
real-time database here so that we know
if there's any kind of vulnerability in
the package and we can stop it from ever
making its way in our codebase. It's
also more than vulnerability detection
and package scanning. We have unified
SCA, SAST, and secrets detection all in
one platform. Your unified verification
layer built on the SonarQube you're
already familiar with for code quality
and SAST, just extended now for
dependencies and AI-generated code, too.
It's genuinely the platform that I lean
on because I have everything I need for
verification in one place. So, if you're
writing code at machine speed now, this
is your ticket to also verify at machine
speed. I'd highly recommend checking it
out. Link in the description. Also, if
you want to get started for free,
standard SonarQube is free for private
projects up to 50,000 lines of code.
I'll link to that as well. Cool. So,
let's zoom in now and see more how this
workflow actually works, how you can use
this for yourself. So, we start with the
exploration step, and the input here,
really the input to the entire workflow,
is a spec document. So, either you'll
craft this by hand or work with a coding
agent to build it. This outlines the
full-stack application that you want to
create. And so, going over to the repo
here, we have all the skills for each
step of the workflow. Again, you can use
your coding agent to help you set up
everything with Pi, with CloudCode,
bringing in all the skills. Our first
one here is the front-end mix explorer.
And so, I'll do command J to open up the
terminal where I have CloudCode already
open in VS Code. And then, since we want
to use Sonnet for this, what we can do
in Claude Code is just do  model.
I can change it to the default, which is
Sonnet. And so, I recommend doing this
for any kind of exploration step in a
workflow cuz you really don't need the
most reasoning capabilities, so we can
make it more token efficient and faster
as well. And then to invoke the skill,
it's just front end mix explore.
And then we can either give it the path
to a spec file like I showed in the
diagram, or it just in quotes here we
can do a free form, you know, like build
XYZ if we want to be more informal. I
would recommend a spec file for a larger
workflow like this building an entire
application, you want to be pretty
specific up front. And so, as far as the
spec file goes, I do actually have a
full example in this repository. So,
this is the exact spec for this
application, the deep space catalog that
I showed earlier. And so, I have the
spec.md here so that we can see the
starting point for the application that
I And then I also have the artifacts, we
can see the full run. Every single one
of the handoff documents produced every
step of the way, I have that documented
so we can look at that really quick as
well. And so, in VS Code, I'll just
right click the spec.md, copy the path,
paste it in here, and then I don't want
to watch paint dry with you, so we're
not going to run this right now. But I'm
just showing you how you would get
started with the workflow for yourself.
You can use this example spec if you
want, or you know, obviously I'd
encourage you to build your own. So,
we'd send that off, and then what we get
out of this skill once the full thing
runs is we have our context.md file.
This is what we then send into the next
planning node. So, we have the repo
state, like here it's actually green
field. Maybe you have some kind of
starter template you want to build on
top of. We have the framework
recommendations, brand assets,
environment variables, data layer. We're
not doing the full planning yet, but
we're just doing the initial surveying
of the spec in the repo, so we have a
good starting point going into the
planning step, so the planning doesn't
have to do as much and we don't have to
spend as many tokens with Opus.
Okay, so back to the diagram now, we
have our context MD and it's time for
the plan step. And again, we do this in
a separate coding agent session. And so
back in Claude Code, we can start up a
new terminal if we want to or we can
just do a slash clear right here. It
really doesn't matter that much. And so
let me open up Claude Code again in a
new session. And this time the skill
that we're going to use is the plan one.
So just slash front-end mix plan. You
can see it, it's really easy here. Like
yes, there's quite a few steps that I
have in this workflow. It'll take a
while to get through it, but you can
chug through this pretty quickly. And
also, it's nice to have different
sessions and different handoff documents
because we can also verify each one. We
can put ourselves in the loop wherever
we want to really make sure the coding
agent is on track. Or if if we want to
just trust it, we can just kind of rip
through these. So we just wait for one
to finish and do the next and then give
the path to the handoff document, right?
So like right here, I'll go back in the
artifacts folder, copy the path to
context.md. That is the one parameter
here. So now we have Opus for our
planning. And I guess before we run
this, we would actually have to do slash
model, right? And switch it back to
Opus. So just make sure you're using the
right model for the right task. And
there's also a lot of work that I put
into engineering the kinds of plans that
are created here. It's a three-section
spec because we have to describe the
information in the UI, how we're going
to do any kinds of integrations like a
back-end or authentication. And then
also, how we're going to deploy the
application. Like if you wanted to hook
up the Digital Ocean or Vercel MCP so
you deploy it automatically, the
workflow can even take care of that for
you. And it's very general, so it works
really no matter the deployment platform
or the back-end you're building,
whatever you're working with. And so
going to the plan here just to keep
following this example of the website I
showed earlier. Section A, the site
content and intent. So this is building
Cosmic Explorer. We describe the voice
and mood, the content and messaging. I
specifically don't want Opus though to
describe the structure of the site in
any way. Like we're going to have grids
in these columns. Like we have none of
that at all because I want to rely on
the strength of Gemini to do that. And
so when I first built this workflow,
Opus tried way too hard. It basically
steamrolled Gemini and told it how to
design the site and it did look
significantly worse. Like it proves that
Gemini is better at building front ends
because when Opus described everything
in the plan, the sites didn't look as
good.
And then we have section B here, so the
integration scope. If we want to build
any kind of API for example, which we
do, we have the Cosmic Explorer back
end. So we have the database for
different planets and things like that.
We have the database model. And then we
also have the deployment plan. And so
right for this example, I don't have any
kind of cloud deployment, but I did do
some testing with it automatically
deploying to Vercel earlier and that
actually worked really really well. So
pretty cool. So that is our plan there.
And so we take the plan.md. We pass it
now into Gemini. This is the fun part
where we get to use Pi or anti-gravity.
And so we have it read the plan, but
specifically just pay attention to
section A. So now we're only building
the UI.
So now back over to my VS Code, I have
Pi open in a terminal now instead of
Claude Code. And so the read me will
guide you through the open router
configuration and the symlink for the
skill and everything. So you can do
/model to switch to Gemini 3.5 flash if
you aren't there already. And then just
/frontend mix design. It's the exact
same as invoking skills in Claude Code.
So even if you're just trying out Pi now
cuz you're interested in this workflow,
very straightforward, it will feel very
similar to you. And so we just have to
give it now the path to our plan.md. So
copy the path here, paste it in, again
just the same. Arguments work the same
with skills in Pi and Claude Code. And
if If want to use anti-gravity instead,
using Gemini 3.5 flash here, you can
just start up a new project in whatever
codebase you're creating this front end,
and then we can just give the path to
the skill. So, I could say, you know,
read the skill here,
and then I'll go back to VS Code, and
I'll I'll actually copy that. So, front
end mix design, and copy the path to the
skill,
and I can say, uh, go through these
instructions now. So, we can literally
use a skill as a prompt, even if you're
using a coding agent that doesn't
support skills in the same way. And then
obviously, we need the path to the plan
as well. Path to the plan is, and then I
can just do the same thing that I did
earlier, copying the path there. And so,
yeah, this might be my ignorance. Maybe
there is a way to do like  front
end mix design, but like even if you
have to tell it to read the skill and
execute the instructions, you can
literally do it this way as well. So,
super easy to invoke this skill, and
then it's going to create the user
interface, and then produce the UI
summary. So, then we can use this to
then go into the integrations and the
rest of the workflow, continuing back
with Claude again.
So now, the rest of the workflow, you
really are just repeating the same
process here. You have the handoff
document that you give as a parameter to
the next node. Just keep in mind that
some of these nodes also might need both
the plan and the previous handoff. And
so, there might be a couple of
arguments, but really everything else is
the exact same. So, I'm not going to go
through and and run through every single
node in this video. I don't think that's
a good use of your time, and I want to
encourage you to just try this out
yourself right now. But, the process is
straightforward all the way to the end
with a smoke test. So, we do the
integrations, like building out any kind
of back end. We do the validation, so
just having Sonic go through our unit
tests and linting and things like that.
We fix any issues that come up with
Opus, and then we have the deployment,
whatever you have in your spec for that.
And then we even do a smoke test. So,
using the agent browser skill, I use
this all of the time. It's browser
automation, so the agent can verify the
website testing it as a user actually
would. So, we do that at the end, and
then we end with a deployed app that as
long as it's not like some really,
really complicated full-stack app,
you're going to have a nice one-shot.
Like, this workflow works incredibly
well from quite a few different tests
that I did with different front ends,
including the one that I showed you
right here that I'm pretty impressed
with overall. So, yeah, I mean, really,
I'm just going to go ahead and leave it
there. I'd encourage you to try this
harness yourself. Even if you just want
to take ideas that I've taught here and
apply it to your own harnesses, of
course, I would encourage you to do that
as well. And so, if you appreciate this
video, you're looking forward to more on
harnesses and agentic engineering, I
would really appreciate a like and a
subscribe. And with that, I will see you
in the next video.